http://www.newsstand.co.uk/privacy/

Sign out
We deliver 1000's of magazines Worldwide!
Change the destination in the dropdown to update the prices displayed on the site. Postage includes
first class delivery in the UK or priority airmail for overseas mail, but please note some children’s
magazines may be dispatched second class where large free gifts are included, to reduce postage costs to
you.
Belarus
Belau (Palau)
British Indian Ocean Territories
British Virgin Is.
Cape Verde
Caymen Is.
Central African Republic
Chad
Chile
China
Christmas Is.
Cocos (Keeling) Is.
Ethiopia
Falkland Is.
Kiribati
Korea (North)
Korea (South)
Norfolk Island
Northern Mariana Is.
Slovenia
Solomon Islands.
Somalia
South Africa
South Georgia
South Sandwich Is.
Spain
Spanish North African Terr.
Turkmenistan
Turks & Caicos Is.
Vietnam
Virgin Is. (US)
Wake Is.
Wallis & Futuna Is.
Foreign Language
JapaneseUS / AmericanFrenchSpanishGermanItalianRussianAsianOther Overseas
Home & Garden
DesignWineCooking & FoodHome InteriorsGardeningBuild & ArchitectureSelf SufficiencyHome EntertainmentDIY
Health & Fitness
CyclingHuntingMindfulnessOffroadGeneral Men'sGeneral Women'sTriathlon & RunningYogaBody & MindSlimmingBodybuildingOther Fitness
Outdoor & Countryside
FarmingFly fishingHuntingCountrysideCamping / Walking / ClimbingHoliday & TravelBoatingYachtingBritishRegional
Crafts & Hobbies
EmbellishHome CraftsSewingTrainsKnitting and CrochetQuiltingBeading & JewelleryScrapbook & Card MakingFlower ArrangingOther CraftsCollectingModellingRailwaysAviationOther TransportRadio ControlIndoor GamesAntiquesPhotographyRadio & ElectronicsWoodworking
Puzzles
ArtSudokuArrowwordCodewordCriss CrossCrosswordLogic PuzzleSudokuWordsearchChildren's PuzzleLarge Print PuzzleOther & Mixed Puzzles
Women's Interest
ArtGlossy FashionWomen's HairWomen's LifestyleWomen's WeeklyBrides & WeddingOlder Women'sParentingYoung Women'sRomantic Fiction
Children's
Childrens EducationalGeneralPre SchoolPrimary BoysPrimary GirlsComicsTeenage GirlsTeenage BoysTeen FashionChildren's Football
Animals & Nature
Men's FashionNaturePoliticsCatsDogsBirdsFishEquestrianWildlifeOther Pets
Arts & Fashion
ColouringHardback FashionLiteratureMen's FashionPhotographyPoliticsLiteraryContemporary ArtVisual ArtsFashionDesignTV & FilmTheatre & Dance
Music & Playing
Classical MusicBlues & Jazz MusicUrban MusicRock MusicPop MusicGuitarHeavy MetalOther
Computers & Gaming
Buying ComputersGeneral GamingSony PlaystationNintendoXboxPC GamingComputer DesignComputer MusicMac ComputerHome PCLinuxPDA & SmartphoneOther Computer
Cars & Bikes
BookazinesRoyal FamilyGeneral CarKit & CustomMarque SpecificMotorsports4x4Classic Car/BikeMotorcyclingMotorcycle SportBikerTruckingCaravanBuying & Selling
Current Affairs & Science
BasketballCultureRoyal FamilyBusiness & FinanceHome EconomicsPoliticalUK Current AffairsIntl Current AffairsSatireScience
Sports
American FootballBaseball BasketballCultureHockeySurfingFootballCricketGame FishingCoarse FishingSea FishingRugbyRing & CombatGolfCyclingMountain Biking/BMXWatersportsWinter SportsIndoor SportsSquash & TennisOtherShooting
Men's Interest
HairMens fashionWeekly MensMens LifestyleHumour & SatireTech & GadgetAlternative & GayWatch
Ethnic
Afro CarribeanAsian
Professional & Trade
CoffeeWineMediaHealth & BeautyAgricultureEducationConstructionOther Trade
Other Interests
BookazinesCelebrities EducationElementumFieraHistoryIndiePromoRoyaltySchoolsTeaAstrologyAstronomyTelevisionCrimeHorrorScience FictionTattooMilitaryGreen LivingReligionSkateboardingMiscellaneousAnnualsPartworksOthers
Back Issues & Bundles
AccentAnorakAnother EscapeAttitudeBack IssuesBeauty PapersBoatBonafideBoneshakerCerealClashClub OenologiqueEco Kids PlanetEight by EightFarewellFashion FanzineFertility RoadFieraFirewordsFoxesGentlemans JournalHappifulHole & CornerHOLE AND CORNERHop and BarleyHouse of CocoIn BloomInternIreland's Military StoryJocks and NerdsJÓNKerrangLagomLike the WindLodestars AnthologyLunch LadyMagnifyMontagudNangNightwatchmanNotionODDAOf The AfternoonOpenhouseOURSPrint Isn't DeadPrinted pagesPrivate EyePuss PussRabonaRaconteur Current AffairsRakesprogressReal ReviewRiposteRoot And BoneSidetrackedSleekSo It GoesSOFFASomesuch StoriesSpoonStar WarsStructoSuitcaseSweet magazineThe GourmandThe LoopThe Rolling HomeTHE WHITE REVIEWTMRWTrack Car PerformanceTurps BananaVestojVNAWeekend JournalsWhite ReviewWorks That WorkWrap
Specials
BookazinesCalendars
CalendarsConfectioneryEW Game of ThronesF/WFWSpecial Covers & Pre-OrdersStamps / Stickers / CollectablesSUITCASE Summer 2014TestWood Briquettes
Gift Ideas
ChristmasDadFashionistasFood LoversGrandmaLittle OnesMagazine StacksMusiciansTeenage BoysTeenage Girls
Graphic Novels, Comics & Manga
ComicsDC comicsGraphic NovelsMangaMarvel comicsGraphic Novels -
Comics & MangaGraphic Novels - Comics & MangaGraphic Novels-Comics & MangaGraphic Novels/Comics & Manga
Best Sellers
Latest Arrivals
Magazine ConciergeBuying a Gift
How It Works
A - B - C - D - E - F - G - H - I - J - K - L - M - N - O - P - Q - R - S - T - U - V - W - X - Y - Z
COVID-19 DELIVERY TIMES
GET THE GOOD NEWS!
From November 1st 2020
All UK post is being delivered in good time and Overseas orders* are being sent by Airmail again!
We've decided to take a financial blow to help get our service to you back to how it should be; speedy overseas delivery, especially in time for Christmas.
Relax, you're travelling in First Class with Newsstand.
Suspended Countries*
Please note that there is no postal service to the following locations at this time:
Azerbaijan, Botswana, Cuba, Haiti, Iraq, Kosovo, Mauritania, Mauritius, Nepal, Paraguay, Turkmenistan, Venezuela, Zambia
Privacy Notice
JG Palmer LLP ("Newsstand" or "we") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We are the data controller and responsible for your personal data.
Our full details are:
JG Palmer LLP
subenquiries@newsstand.co.uk
37 St. Margarets Street, Canterbury, Kent, CT1 2TU
This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed. Please read the following carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.
Newsstand may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. This policy is effective from 17 May 2018.
Your rights
1.1	You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection (www.ico.org.uk). We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with any concern before you approach the ICO so please contact us in the first instance.
1.2	Under certain circumstances you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data. You have the right to:
Request access to your personal data (commonly known as a "data subject access request"). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.
Request correction of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.
Request erasure of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where you have successfully exercised your right to object to processing (see below), where we may have processed your information unlawfully or where we are required to erase your personal data to comply with local law. Note, however, that we may not always be able to comply with your request of erasure for specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at the time of your request.
Object to processing of your personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which override your rights and freedoms.
Request restriction of processing of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your personal data in the following scenarios: (a) if you want us to establish the data's accuracy; (b) where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (c) where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or (d) you have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.
Request the transfer of your personal data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you. Withdraw consent at any time where we are relying on consent to process your personal data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.
If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please contact us.
No fee usually required
You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.
What we may need from you
We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.
Time limit to respond
We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.
What we collect
We may collect the following information that you give to us by filing in forms on our site when you search for products, place an order, subscribe/set up an account with us, enter a competition, promotion or survey, or by corresponding with us by phone, email or otherwise:
Name
Contact information including email address and telephone numbers;
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests;
Information about your subscriptions, such as delivery locations and magazines subscribed to; and
Financial and credit card information.
With regard to each of your visits to our site, we will automatically collect the following information:
technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, and operating system and platform;
information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL), clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time), products you viewed or searched for' page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs),methods used to browse away from the page, and any phone number used to call our customer service number.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to, fulfil any contract we have with you, to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
We use your name, contact information, subscription and financial information to carry out our obligations arising from any purchases you make (including the handling of complaints, performance of post-sales services, administration of orders and accounts and shipping) and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;
We use your name, email address and information about your completed purchases to provide you with emails containing new magazine issue covers, "Cover Alerts", only on the magazines that you have purchased from us in the past. This is in our legitimate interest to develop our products and services and grow our business.
Publishers may also contact you by electronic means if you have consented to this (see below for Disclosure of your information). If you do not want us to use your data in this way, please ensure that the relevant boxes are left unticked when you proceed to the checkout);
We use your name and contact information to contact you for market research purposes by email, phone, fax or mail. This is in our legitimate interest to develop our products and services and grow our business.
We may use your subscription, technical information and information about your visit to customise the website according to your interests. This is necessary in our legitimate interests to grow our business;
We use your name, subscription and contact information to notify you about changes to our service. This is necessary for the performance of any contract we have with you and to comply with our legal obligations;
We use your technical information to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. This is necessary in our legitimate interests to grow our business.
We use your technical information and information about your visit for analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes. This is necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise);
We use your technical information to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so. This is in our legitimate interest to develop our products and services and grow our business.;
We use your name, contact, subscription, financial and technical information as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure. This is necessary to comply with our legal obligations and for our legitimate interests (running our business, network security and to prevent fraud);
We use your name, contact, subscription and technical information as well as information about your visit to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising Newsstand serves to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you. This is necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our marketing strategy);
We use your name, contact, subscription and technical information as well as information about your visit to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about products that may interest you or them. This is necessary in our legitimate interests to grow our business.
Customers can change their marketing preferences at any time by logging in to their account and selecting "My Newsstand".
You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by following the opt-out links on any marketing message sent to you or by contacting us or the third party, as appropriate, at any time.
Where you opt out of receiving these marketing messages it will not apply to personal data provided to us as a result of a product purchase or other transactions.
Disclosure of your information
You agree that, by consenting to us sharing your data with the publisher(s) of the magazines that you purchase, those publishers may contact you in relation to other products and services including relevant content, offers and promotions.
You agree that, by consenting to us processing your personal data, that we have the right to share your personal information with any member of or group, as well as analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvements and optimisation of our site. In addition, we will disclose your personal information to third parties:
In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
If JG Palmer LLP or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of JG Palmer LLP, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
For auditing purposes, we may share your personal data with a third-party auditing organisation (ABC) so they can verify aggregated statistics about circulation and usage of our Publisher's products or review their policies, processes and procedures for compliance with relevant standards. You can view their Privacy Policy by following this link; ABC Privacy Policy
Where we store your personal data
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
1.3	Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How long we retain your personal data
We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.
To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements. By law we have to keep basic information about our customers (including name, contact, financial and subscription information) for six years after they cease being customers for tax purposes. We will only retain your technical information and information about your visit for three years after that visit.
How we use cookies
1.4	Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual.
We use the following cookies:
Login 'remember me' Cookie (if checked on log-in), enabling you to remain signed in until you manually sign-out of the service. The cookie will be removed upon sign-out, or if you have not visited the site for a period of more than one year.
Basket Information (if not signed in), enabling previous products that you have added to your basket to be remembered. Cookie removed when a successful login has been completed, or a period of one year, whichever is sooner.
Tracking referral site information so we can better identify where traffic is coming from.
Third party Cookie from the Google Analytics service, enabling us to track the flow of users through the Newsstand Site, in aid of improving our service. Please refer to Google’s privacy policy for more details.
Third party Cookie from Twitter, enabling Twitter to track the flow of users through the Newsstand Site, in aid of improving our service. Please refer to Twitter's privacy policy for more details.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Please note that third parties (including, publishers) may also use cookies, over which we have no control.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Copyright © 2020 Newsstand
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
The current issue of
is currently out of stock
However, we can try and order a copy in for you if you would like us to.
If so, please enter your email below and we will let you know if this issue becomes available and you can then decide to purchase it or not.
NB: We may not succeed so please consider ordering the next issue.
Email:
Request this issue
Cancel
